\leftarrow

Michele Snow

15 New Line, Cootehill, Co. Cavan | 086 8880237| michelesnowy15@gmail.com

PROFILE

I am well organised and have good communication skills and work ethic, I am always punctual and willing to learn new skills. I am flexible, eager and willing to add to my knowledge base and skills. I have experience in childcare and a hotel setting and working on shift rotation. I am pursuing a childcare assistant role where I can help develop children both mentally and physically.

KEY SKILLS

- Good communication skills
- Patient, caring and compassionate
- Determination and persistence
- Excellent team player

WORK EXPERIENCE

Care Assistant | Drumlin House 2015 to 2016

- Providing the highest standard of hygiene for patients
- Showering, hoisting and supervising patients
- Walking and cooking for patients
- Providing excellent customer service

Childcare Assistant | Fingers & Toes Community Childcare, Latton, Monaghan 2013 to 2014

- Assisting children with their homework aged 5 years of age to 12
- Helping teachers with creating lesson plans and maintaining a safe environment in the classroom
- Keeping all areas clean and tidy throughout the day and ensuring the sanitation is safely disinfected
- Communicating with parents and knowing how to deal with an emergency situation
- Prepare and serve meals; monitoring the children throughout mealtimes
- Group activities with approx. 25 children

Catering Assistant | Darley Day Care Centre, Cootehill, Co. Cavan

2007 to 2010

In charge of kitchen duties: cleaning, serving and organising meal times Interacting with the residents and organising activities Covering holiday and sickness leave

Childcare Assistant | Little Stars Afterschool Club, Cootehill, Cavan 2009

2005 to

- Carrying out duties and interacting with children aged 6 months to 5 years of age
- Group activities: sport, art & craft, walking and board games
- Preparing healthy snacks for approx. 10 children

Catering assistant in various establishments

1989 to 2005

EDUCATION & QUALIFICATIONS

Healthcare Assistant – QQI level 5 – Cavan Institute 2016–to date

Child Development – level 6 – Cavan Institute 2014 - 2015

Teaching Assistant (CTA 3) – CACHE level 3 – Cavan Institute 2006 – 2007

Childcare – FETAC level 5 – Cavan Institute 2005 – 2006

Computer Applications – level 4 & 5 – Cavan Institute 2004 – 2005

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Garda Vetted for Care Assistant - December 2016 Manual Handling - 2016 First Aid (including CPR & AED) - 2016

INTERESTS

I help out with local fundraising for charity events and take part in sponsored walks.

REFERENCES

References available on request.

Page